# **NKOSINATHI**

# **MTSHALI**

## **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

#### **PROFILE**

I am writing to express my interest in the Full-Stack Developer position at your Company. As a full-stack developer with experience in Java, Ionic, Python, and Angular, I am confident that I have the skills and expertise necessary to excel in this role.

In my current position at TcF lcT, I have been responsible for developing and maintaining web applications using a variety of technologies. I have experience working with both front-end and back-end development, and I am comfortable working with databases, APIs, and other tools necessary for building complex web applications.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### TcF IcT

2020 - PRESENT

Software Developer

- Building dynamic and adaptable web applications
- Performing analysis of product development
- Working with back-end programmers to create REST API
- Creating user interfaces using the AngularJS framework
- Collaborating with other developers, managers, and UX designers in building software

MLAB 2019 - 2020

Intern then Software Developer

- · Building dynamic and adaptable web applications using Angular Developing
- cross-platform mobile applications with a native-like experience using lonic
- Delivering comprehensive front-end software
- Working with back-end programmers to create REST API
- Creating user interfaces using the AngularJS framework

### **Projects**

- Tipper Mobile App
- · Henkel (Safety equipment system)
- Hats and Shoulders App
- Pre-school App
- Mthomhowolwazi App
- Print Pics App
- Law App

### REFERENCE

# Fabian Qopane Ekurhuleni West College

Computer Science Lecture

Phone 073 457 5813

Nokwanda Mrajane Mlab

Senior Developer and Facilitate

Phone: 072 188 3914

## CONTACT

- **6** 069-135-5034
- ✓ 9mm.ext.gp@gmail.com
- **Q** 2367 Rabie Ridge, Midrand



### **EDUCATION**

## 2015 - 2017 EKURHULENI WEST COLLEGE

 Computer Sciences and Information Technology

2019 - 2020

- Angular & Ionic
- RestFull API's
- No SQL Database

### 2021 - 2022

### **UMUZI**

**MLAB** 

- Python
- MvSQL

### **SKILLS**

- Project Management
- Public Relations
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Design Skills

### LANGUAGES

English (Fluent)